var questions = [
    {
        question:"What did Peter Quill steal on Morag? ?",
        answers:["egg","Gamora","A spaceship","The power stone"],
        correctAnswer: "The power stone"
    },
    {
        question:"a cria is a baby what?",
        answers:['llama',"hedgehog","pangolin","iguana"],
        correctAnswer: "llama"
    },
    {
        question:"About how many bears exist in the world?",
        answers:["1 million","500 thousand", "20 million", "100 thousand"],
        correctAnswer: "1 million"
    },
    {
        question:"if canine means dog-like, and feline means cat-like, what does aqualine mean?",
        answers:["manatee-like","eagle-like", "donkey-like", "fish-like"],
        correctAnswer: "eagle-like"
    },
    {
        question:"which of these words means crab-like?",
        answers:["caprine","cancerine", "bubaline", "murine"],
        correctAnswer: "cancerine"
    },
    {
        question:"What is the largest species of penguin?",
        answers:["emperor","fairy", "chinstrap", "king"],
        correctAnswer: "emperor"
    },
    {
        question:"What do you call a group of parrots?",
        answers:["a parliment","a pandemonium", "a prickle", "a pride"],
        correctAnswer: "a pandemonium"
    },
    {
        question:"What do you call a group of jellyfish?",
        answers:["a smack","a slap", "a crash", "a splash"],
        correctAnswer: "a smack"
    },
    {
        question:"What do you call a group of unicorns?",
        answers:["a blessing","a miracle", "a surprise", "a boon"],
        correctAnswer: "a blessing"
    },
    {
        question:"What do you call a group of ravens?",
        answers:["an unkindness","a congress", "a business", "an organization"],
        correctAnswer: "an unkindness"
    },
]